(Leonard:)Is that a pregnancy test?
(Penny:)Just the first one.
I didn't save them all.
(Leonard:)I can't believe
I read this table wrong.
(Sheldon:)I blame you.
(Amy:)Me? What did I do?
(Sheldon:)You distract me.
(Sheldon:)I've been distracted
since the moment I met you.
(Howard:)-Sorry.
-Well, you should be.
(Sheldon:)Because all I can think about
is how much I want to kiss you.
(Sheldon:)And not just on the cheek,
but on the mouth.
(Sheldon:)Like mommies and daddies do.
(Amy:)Oh, Sheldon.
(Sheldon(not in Amy's daydream, now in the Cheesecake Factory):)Amy?
(Sheldon(not in Amy's daydream, now in the Cheesecake Factory):)Amy? Did you hear what I said?
(Sheldon:)Can't talk, in the zone.